"뉴저지 동부 러더포드의 게이, 레즈비언, 양성애자, 성전환자 연합 5주년 파티"
"The Fifth Annual East Rutherford,New Jersey,Gay,Lesbian,Bisexual and Transgender Alliance Luau."
오, 시장이 더 넓어졌는걸 대머리 게이들 말이야
Oh,another market to expand into-- balding gay men.
그리고 레즈비언은 블루투스를 좋아한다니까
And I'll bet lesbians love Bluetooth.
우린 가서 일해야 돼
We should get to work.
잠깐, 잠깐, 잠깐, 왜 여기 '하루 배송'이라고 써 있어?
Wait,wait,why does it say "one-day rush"?
도대체 언제 우리가 하루 배송을 하겠다고 그랬는데?
Since when do we offer a one-day rush?
아마존이 하루만에 배송해 주지
Amazon offers one-day rush.
그래, 하지만 걔네들은 책들을 풀로 붙일 필요가 없잖아
Yeah,but they don't have to glue the books together.
도대체 어떻게 하루만에 천 개의 페니 블라섬을 만들 수 있겠어?
How the hell are we going to make a thousand Penny Blossoms in one day?